Are you ready to live the life you deserve?
Don't Worry Darling is a science fiction, mystery,
thriller film directed by Olivia Wilde.
Alice and Jack are lucky to be living in the idealized community of Victory, the experimental company
town housing the men who work for the top-secret Victory Project and their families.
But when cracks in their idyllic life begin to appear, exposing flashes of something much more sinister lurking
beneath the attractive façade, Alice can’t help questioning exactly what they’re doing in Victory, and why.
Alice, played by Florence Pugh.
Jack, played by Harry Styles.
Frank, played by Chris Pine.
Bunny, played by Olivia Wilde.
Margaret, played by KiKi Layne.
Shelley, played by Gemma Chan.
Don't Worry Darling is a 2022 American psychological thriller film directed by Olivia Wilde from a
screenplay by Katie Silberman, based on a spec script by brothers Carey Van Dyke and Shane Van Dyke.
Starring Florence Pugh, Harry Styles, Olivia Wilde, Gemma Chan, KiKi Layne, Nick Kroll, and Chris Pine, it follows a housewife in an
idyllic company town who begins to suspect a sinister secret being kept from its residents by the man who runs it.
Following the critical success of Wilde's feature directorial debut Booksmart (2019), a multi-studio
bidding war took place for her second film, with New Line Cinema eventually winning.
Pugh joined the cast in April 2020, with Styles added that September,
replacing Shia LaBeouf after production had already begun.
Filming took place in Los Angeles from October 2020 to February 2021.
The film was the subject of media attention and controversy, including conflicting reports regarding
the circumstances of LaBeouf's departure and alleged conflicts between Wilde and Pugh.
Don't Worry Darling premiered at the 79th Venice International Film Festival on September 5, 2022,
and was theatrically released in the United States on September 23 by Warner Bros.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $87.6 million.
The film explores themes of suburbian idyll, cult, palm
springs, psychological thriller, stepford wife.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and thought_provoking.